bitext.com 2016-08-02

# Privacy Policy for bitext.com

[Bitext](https://www.bitext.com/) » Privacy Policy for bitext.com

We respect your right to privacy and feel it is important for you to know how we handle the information we receive from you via our Site or via any other media at [http://www.bitext.com](http://www.bitext.com/) (the “Site”) or the rest of our online services and demos (the “Service”).

#### COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

When you register for our Site or our Service, we ask for information such as your name, company name and address, e-mail address and phone number. You can also visit our site anonymously.

Bitext may use the collected personal information and other information Bitext collects about your use of our Site and our Service to operate and make the Service available to you, for billing, identification and authentication, to contact you about your use of the Service, research purposes and to generally improve the content and functionality of the Service and Site and for announcements about products and offers by email. You retain all rights to your data.

#### USE OF INFORMATION

We use the information we collect about you (including your Personally Identifiable Information) to offer our services, create a better, more personalized experience for you based on your individual usage habits, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our site’s content, layout and services.

#### SHARING OF INFORMATION

Except as described in this policy, Bitext will not give, sell, rent, or loan any identifiable personal information to any third party. We may disclose such information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may also share such information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law. Bitext may assign or transfer this privacy policy, and your user account and related information and data, to any person or entity that acquires or is merged with Bitext.

#### REVIEWING, UPDATING, DELETING AND DEACTIVATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will modify, update and personalize your Personally Identifiable Information upon your request via our contact page. Also, upon your request we will deactivate your account and remove your Personally Identifiable Information from our active databases.

Nonetheless, we may retain in our files information you may have requested us to remove if, in our sole discretion, retention of the information is necessary to resolve disputes or troubleshoot problems. Furthermore, your information may never be completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints.

#### PROTECTION OF INFORMATION

Bitext maintains reasonable security measures to protect your information from loss, destruction, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure. These technologies help ensure that your data is safe, secure, and only available to you and to those you provided authorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

#### CHANGES

Bitext may update this policy from time to time. You can review the most current version of this privacy policy at any time at [http://www.bitext.com](http://www.bitext.com/). Your continued use of the Site or Service constitutes your agreement to be bound by such changes to the privacy policy. Your only remedy, if you do not accept the terms of this privacy policy, is to discontinue use of the Site and Service. You can send us your questions about this policy via our contact page.
